Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel PSP. Today we are going to
talk about the ICICI Group of Companies. There are
four companies listed in the market -
ICICI Bank Loan, Birthday Special, and
Securities - whose names are in front of you. The
six-month and one-year returns are in front of you.
Nifty has made six percent in six months
and 20 percent in one year.
ICICI Bank has
used the fee to outperform,
and this is very good.
Subscribe. And as seen here in the last, there has been a
significant decline in the market. So, in such a situation,
what should be our strategy for this group? We are going to
discuss the
first stock we will talk about.
ICICI Bank has a
huge market cap of Rs 5 lakh crore. The last
date price is Rs 736. It has taken 2030 years.
In financial stocks, the period is more
important. So, the price of ICICI Bank
is around the purchasing power, which will
not be very expensive, nor can it be called very cheap. If we
talk about the final product of the company, you will see that it looks quite good.
Benefits You will get by clicking the
subscribe button
in many problems due to the commission, so it took
time to do it, do not do it, there was a
decline in the stock but it is seen moving back towards the company, the
four major markets clearly show
that there has been a decline in the stock from the level of 850
and the strongest stop is
seen taking support, currently the stock
is below the moving average of 2450 country, the
moving average of one race seems intact for the bill, the
moving average of Twenty20 is out,
its chart is very
strong, click, if you
look at Bank Nifty, Bank Nifty has already broken its two-
day moving average two-three days ago,
whereas in ICICI Bank, the
moving average of hedge seems intact, so
here you see a good sponge, if we
talk about the Belia relationship,
Delhi RSI is 25.18, we will
not do much, but regarding the World Cup, it
seems to be developing a little, there is a
decline in the weekly chart that war, so  It
tries to subscribe a little bit. There
is a similar situation.
Talking about the weekly RSS, the last time it was
15.07, it has been moving above six for some time
because the momentum was
going very well here, but there was a
clear decline. It also came down so much that a recovery was visible, then it went
around six. After taking resistance,
it was seen coming down again. This is a side
signal. Talking about the monthly chart, the
monthly chart still shows a lot of upside
and the momentum
is strong because the
subscription has
decreased, but there is
ghee. The
10-inch moving average on the monthly chart is
visible around the road.
We also see interest in this. So if we
talk about support here, then the strong support
is visible, a very
strong support. We can expect
that the stock will not go below this, but
unfortunately, we cannot guarantee anything. So, if
you grow with two supports, then the
first support is the strongest
support at six. Services 201 good.  Support
is where we can expect the
stock to readjust and
try to move back up. After that, we
see the six-digit level. I would
also like to clarify both of these. First of all,
why is it
important to educate yourself about this? Look here, it
took resistance, then saw a decline.
Then it went back up, so it spent a good amount of
time.
After taking support here twice, the stock
took support in this very zone and we saw a rise again. So
this will become very important.
Its 2-second moving average is close to this. The
next support that will be seen is the
joint revision of this.
Short-term resistance was
seen here. The stock did not go above this for
about a month. After that, there were
attempts to break here. Then when the
top came back up, even after taking support here,
we saw it moving up. So, one is a
two-eye zone and the other is a see zone,
which you can see in the pot. So,
for the long term, the bank is good and is
placed here.  Keep doing this, the
subscribe button goes, I have
told you in this video that I was so
disgusted,
now I have
fixed the screen but
subscribe and as per today's date, the
size of the bank, the group of the bank, in
that way the valuation
cannot be very expensive, so
both the parties can think about revaluation,
second is ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance Company, the market price is 567, the
last rate price is 127, it
seems a little expensive for the festival, if we
talk about the financial trend, then
you will see that a huge
jump has been seen in the revenue, but
you have seen the profitability decreasing for the last 4 years, if you
look at other insurance
companies, then you were appointed in pregnancy, they do
not take profit, there is
no problem here, but
profit is seen to be happening, points
6206, so this is not at all home, I
clearly show on Ek Totka channel
that the stock is falling the most
and the stocks are currently
around 550  It is seen straightening and
is below all its moving averages,
whose moving average was
also seen coming below the moving average of the stars, so the gains are
quite high and have been going on for quite some time, the
belly is below Rs.50,
indicating growth. Talking about the weekly chart,
you will see that the
stock has seen good growth at present,
after the month, the trend was good, that is why there was a good trend,
after that the strike was seen
breaking its old all-time high and going up to 700,
but a decline is being seen again, it is
around its middle moving average, it is trying to take support.
Talking about the weekly RSS, the
weekly of 14.82 is coming, the party
's clearance of F-35 is clear, such is a
good time when Wittek
can think about investing, we will
talk about support, important support, the
biggest support will be its old all-
time level, it is here and has
reached the desktop, it is not far away, it has
also touched there, let's take a look at the recovery.  The
moving average of this contest is also
visible in the middle, so this frill 550
song is a good support, another reason for this is
that the big green candle seen here will
try to take support at its higher end,
by chance it breaks, then
which support will be seen after that, so
frankly speaking, these
teachers see support, its
hatred where we were here for some of our very time,
after which we withdrew that it can be seen
and this till is seen around 130,
so
subscribe here, if you
want to do it, then you can adopt here, you made
one installment at 50, after that
you made the second installment around 450,
although I personally believe that
if you want to invest in insurance companies, then
we have a better company available than this, its
profit which you
see decreasing after clicking on continue, I did
not like that here, that is why I
prefer to subscribe and its
value does not come at all, it is also very
high
and
looks better,
third  ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company has a
market cap of 6700. Its free look period
is 3157. The last price of the year was
not very expensive and not very cheap either. If we
talk about the final product, then
you should
subscribe and have been doing well
in the last 4 years. On the
chart of the stock, it is clearly visible
that the stock saw a decline from the 1615 level
and the free stock is trading at 3155. There has been a
significant decline. It is
seen below all its moving averages. The
Twenty20 moving average has already
crossed the crossword, the moving average of the face has
also crossed it and the moving average of the hundreds
also seems to be preparing that
it will also come below the moving average of the desk. If we
talk about the ultimate beans, it is visible on the accused.
It had a very important
support which was around the fish, it
looked like psychological, but here
and
subscribed from here, so this also
This scene was seen breaking,
this tube
sky was seen, so if
you want to invest here then you
can think about investing, the company is
good, the company looks very good, it has taken over
Indian General Insurance in
March, due to which its business has also
increased, if we talk about private companies then
General Insurance Limited
is the number one company, you should invest in it, you should
subscribe, you
can think about investing because
it is
very important for you,
so you
can do it here, if you want to do it here, it does
not seem far away,
subscribe up here, you can get a
chance to make the second installment here, so you
can invest here, the
problem is that investing can be very
risky, overtime you should
think about investing here, so firstly the
current market price is 1350 and
secondly you
can think about investing more, these
four stocks are ICICI Securities
Limited
2000, its market cap is 75, the last date
price is 19.3, which is available at a decline of half percent  If the
price is of Rs. 1000 then valuation
wise it appears to be very cheap to you.
Talking about the financial plan,
you will see that 2018-1922 financial year was
not that special, revenue was coming down
and you saw profits fluctuating
but after the court, a
very good momentum has been seen in growing
Rotting Hormone
Subscribe because there is a lot of
posted subscribe
profit here, it is visible here after a good deal.
On the chart of A talk, it is clearly visible
that only the stock saw a decline
and the Shilale strike is seen to be 750 favorite, the
balance came down and
after that, you will see this body doing its work and it is
straightening around 150, 2453,
its moving average is
seen to be flat and is straightening below it,
desk moving and till these tax havens,
whose morning you see is very far away, then the
most technical strength is seen, if
you
also see on the Parag Appointment Early Appointment of ICICI Securities, then it is very high
but
here  But if you see more, the page
appears close to educated, it is not a fast,
but the organization will not do it around the village, that is
Yuvraj, you should click here, you can
think about doing it,
but I believe that for the long term,
such a good company,
subscribe company, will
perform well if there is momentum in the market, if there is a decline on the side, then
here, now
look at the school, how the decline happened here, it is
very visible to the youth, it is
difficult to tell whether
this trend of youth association continues, then it will go up, but
I believe that whenever there is a
slight correction in the market, like the 10 percent
correction that has happened now, if it goes on for another six-eight months, then there are
many
investors here who will exit the market
and new investors will also stop coming, hence
I believe that you can prepare here, you can
prepare a position, but for the very
long term, in my opinion, the
entire sector will remain very volatile,
if you want to invest, then what are the
levels where you should keep an eye, the
first support is visible here  There is
good support around the chart verses, you
can see this, this whole thing is
seen like a raw support, so you
can think about buying here, you
can make the first installment off, although
I have told you my view,
after this the major support that will be seen is the
level below the road, which is its all-time
high, old all-time, there is an edge
visible there, so if you want to regulate here then you
can think about doing it,
these four stocks are Idea group stocks,
Welcome group, so there should be maximum gravity here, the
bank has a market of 5 lakh crores, so
we should focus
more there, you can think about investing there,
after that if you want to invest then you
can keep an eye on Prudential on Monday, ICC, as per the focus, there should be
more on ICICI Bank
because it is well established, the
chances of a fall there are less,
you will get more, do subscribe to this channel,
thank you